Okay people let's react to a
bueno gente vamos a reaccionar a un
video it's funny because we're going to
vídeo es curioso porque vamos a
react to a podcast from the
reaccionar a un podcast de la
competition and Jordi Gual the
competencia competencia y jordi gual el
other day in one of his
otro día en uno de sus extractos de
live podcast excerpts said that his
directo de podcast ha dicho que su
garbage in high school he
basura en el secundario
was talking about Top Gamers Academy and you
estuvo hablando de top gamers academy y
've sent me a lot of
me habéis mandado muchísimo por email
that video by email so that I can react to it, I haven't
ese vídeo para que los reacciones no he
seen absolutely anything I promise you about
visto absolutamente nada os lo prometo
the video let's relate it and see
del vídeo vamos a relacionarlo y a ver
what you think about the subject I'm really
qué opinas sobre el tema me da muchísima
curious I'm really curious
curiosidad me da muchísima curiosidad
because I've seen Jordi Guay be
porque yo he visto jordi guay ser
quite critical
bastante crítico
of this type of reality show with
con este tipo de reality con la
television itself but on the other hand
televisión en sí pero por otra parte
I'm curious what he's going to say about
tengo curiosidad de qué va a decir sobre
the program
el programa
and if suddenly I'm going to be surprised that
y si de repente me va a sorprender que
having his friends or acquaintances there who are not
al estar ahí amigos suyos o conocidos no
colleagues from YouTube speaks well of the
colegas de youtube hable bien ahora del
program now I don't know let's see what he
programa no lo sé vamos a ver qué es lo
says
que dice
[Music]
[Música]
yesterday a reality show called Top
ayer se estrenó un reality llamado top
Gamers Academy premiered which is a reality show where
gamers academy que es un reality donde
this
están metidos youtuber star tiene este
man, Bielsa and Kin are involved, two views this
hombre a bielsa y kin two views esta
crest, Ángel Rangel, very handsome, bangente
cresta ángel rangel guapísimo bangente
I want a curiosity is given
quiero una curiosidad es habida cuenta
one thing is that those from the gamer
de una cosa y es que los de todo gamer
academy
academy
have wanted to be very inclusive, they are not
han querido ser muy inclusivos ellos no
like, let's put the number here, the
en plan vamos a meter aquí el número el
same number of girls as boys,
mismo número de chicas que de chicos
okay, but nevertheless, the 3
vale pero sin embargo a los 3
YouTubers and their three assistants, the six
youtube y sus tres ayudantes a los seis
judges have been chosen as men because they have
jueces los han cogido hombres porque han
chosen three men and three women, I'm
cogido tres hombres y tres mujeres
not going to answer because in reality they
no lo voy a contestar porque en realidad
don't care about inclusiveness, those
no les importa lo inclusivo esos
posturings as always came out of it,
postureo como siempre lo salía de hace
in reality what matters to them are the
en realidad lo que le importa son los
numbers,
números
okay,
vale
my idol Angel, my friend, crack, more people
mi ídolo ángel amigo crack más gente
involved in the world of gaming, it is presented by
metida del mundo del gaming lo presenta
Jordi Cruz, art attack power and well, I don't
jordi cruz art attack power y bueno no
know if you've seen it and what you thought, you didn't see it, I've
sé si la has visto y qué te pareció no
seen it, I've seen a couple of
las viste lo he visto ha visto un par de
comments on Twitter and such, but they won't
comentarios en twitter y tal pero que no
be good, that's
serán buenos
what usually happens, what it takes is a
es lo que suele pasar lo que coge es un
format that you know works on YouTube
formato que sabes que en youtube
but on television,
funciona pero en la televisión
I was contacted by those from, I think it was
a mí me contactaron los de los de creo
them, they didn't tell me the name,
que eran ellos no me dijeron el nombre
top games, but a few
top games pero me contactó hace unos
months ago, a production company contacted me that wanted to make a
meses una productora que quería hacer un
reality show with male gamers, two plus two, it
reality con gamers hombre en dos más dos
has to be them, by balls, very
tienen que ser ellos por [__] muy
well, eh, to do something with me, I
bien eh para para hacer algo conmigo yo
at first i understood that they wanted us
al principio entendí que querían que nos
youtubers to get in there as
metiéramos los youtubers ahí dentro como
contestants I said no not even flaix the
de concursantes dije que ni de flaix la
truth is that my life is going too well right now
verdad que mi vida ahora mismo me va muy
to spend 23 months in one it
bien como para meterme 23 meses en una
seems very strange to me that they wanted to
me resulta muy extraño que hayan querido
contact jordi white
contactar a jordi white
but I also wanted to say before
pero también quería contar antes que a
rubio grave or willy
rubio grave o willy
today I am going to handle the people that you are
hoy voy a manejar a la gente que estáis
putting in the chanquete it is me in the
poniendo en el chanquete soy yo en el
future
futuro
ivan who has asked me for art
iván que me ha pedido al arte
but that is not enjoyed while years
pero que no se disfruta mientras años
before willy rue blues and they are going to
sea antes que a willy rue blues y van a
want to call jordi white who still
querer llamar a jordi white que sigue
has a number also not as much as them
tiene número también no tanto como ellos
and also jordi is not a gamer
y además jordi no es gamer
in fact the games that he plays from time
de hecho a los juegos que juega de vez
to time are beings in quite
en cuando son seres en juegos bastante
strange games maybe sometime he decides to
raros a lo mejor alguna vez que le dé
play a gamer game no I
por jugar un juego de gamer no
mean they go because I can't know no
o sea que van porque no puedo saberlo no
but I found the house curious
pero me ha resultado curioso la casa
but they told me no although it was more
pero me dijeron que no aunque era más
to do other things the truth is that
para hacer otras cosas la verdad es que
I am not sincere either I was not very
tampoco soy sincero no tenía mucho
interested I am not very into reality shows of this
interés no soy muy de realities de este
type and it stayed there a bit
tipo de realities y se quedó hay un poco
stopped and in the end well I don't know what they wanted
parado y al final pues no sé qué querían
and if they wanted me to present something that
e si querían que presentara algo que
was one of the youtubers like
fuera uno de los de los youtubers como
this one, Rubio is such a good one, I was there there are
está rubio es tal estuviera yo ahí hay
people that I like a lot, I think there are
gente que me gusta mucho creo que hay
people very good measure the little that I have
gente muy buena medida lo poco que he
seen I have seen little but I have seen little I have
visto he visto poco pero poco he visto
not liked it and I have not liked it not
no me ha gustado y no me ha gustado no
because of the people that are there because I think it is
por la gente que hay porque creo que
worth a lot they do not have much to
vale muchísimo no tienen mucho que
prove they are people who are more than
demostrar ya son gente que está más que
consolidated but we are in the same
consolidada pero estamos en lo de
old thing the
siempre
classic youtuber format on television
el formato youtuber clásico en la tele
remains to adhere to but Javi as you know
queda adherirse pero javi como sabéis
they called Jordi before Rugby
que llamaron a jordi antes que al rugby
and Willy because if Jordi had been there they would
y willy pues porque si jordi hubieras
not have called any of
estado no hubieran llamado a alguno de
the others no
los otros no
if they were calling Jordi it is because
si estaban llamando a jordi es porque
the others had not confirmed yet it is
los otros no habían confirmado todavía
not
no
tacky and it is what it is even when he
está cutre y es lo que es incluso cuando
praised it and today consumer that I am not going to
la elogió y hoy consumer que no lo voy a
bring him here to the wild project we have already
traer aquí al the wild project ya lo
talked about it I love it he is an
hemos hablado me encanta es una leyenda
absolute legend the way you flip he made a
absoluta la vía que flipas hizo un
program and Sevilla is tacky I do not know what happens
programa y sevilla cutre no sé qué pasa
with him form especially those well the
con él forma sobre todo esas pues el
problem Carlos that I think when they
problema carlos que yo creo cuando se
try to imitate the format  youtube to
intenta imitar el formato youtube a la
tv is a [ __ ] I always heard that the
tele es una [__] siempre escuché eso el
program that made the ear
programa que hizo el oído
but I don't know what program it is
pero no sé qué programa es
what program made the hole
qué programa hizo el hoyo
wise men I have fallen for tv
sabios he caído a la tele
but what program made
pero que el programa hecho
because these are like dubbing no
porque estos son como doblajes no
then the sushi monologue
luego el monólogo de sushi
to hell what I would have to do is
a la [__] lo que tendría que hacer es
take someone from youtube and give them a
[__] a alguien del youtube y darle un
television program and
programa de televisión y que lo
present it as what they do they provoked
presentará como lo que hace provocaron
the resistance with that a univa aura and
la resistencia con eso un aura univa y
I people of a serious people of this
yo gente de un grave gente de este
style that communicate well we could
estilo que comunica bien podríamos
do it because in the end what we do
hacerlo porque al final lo que hacemos
is this but in a room in one in a
es esto pero en una habitación en uno en
house but that we are already people who are
una casa pero eso ya ya somos gente que
noted that we have a communicative gift
se nota que tenemos un don comunicativo
and a way of speaking
y una forma de hablar
well you would have to see them you would have to
bueno habría que verlos habría que
seeing me I would love to present a
viendo a mí me encantaría presentar un
television program for I would
programa de televisión para me
love to but you would have to see it's worth it
encantaría pero habría que ver os vale
because one thing is for you to be at the
porque una cosa es que tú este en el
desk in your environment talking to
escritorio en tu ambiente hablando con
your followers or whatever you do each one
tus seguidores o lo que hagáis cada uno
when you are direct because in
cuando seáis directo porque esto de
fact Jordi you do this recorded
hecho jordi tú lo haces grabado
I would like to see you doing it live
me gustaría verte haciéndolo en directo
that unforeseen events arise okay I would
que te surjan improvistos vale me
like to see you debating with someone live
gustaría verte debatiendo con alguien en
I would like  to see you as a mediator in a
me gustaría verte de mediador en un
live debate where you see the
debate en directo ahí donde se ve los
skills of if a person takes a
dotes de si una persona se lleva un
program to entertain knowing how to get out of
programa para entretener saber salir del
open steps the other is fine but you
pasos abiertos el otro vale pero que tú
tell me what
me digas a mí qué
Aurum play because he does the live shows
aurum play porque hace los directos
playing at love which I'm not saying no
jugando al amor que no digo que no
either but no but we already know I'm going to do
tampoco pero no pero sabemos ya voy a
using love or grace who does
hacer utilizando el amor o grace que
the live shows playing at oven yesterday you're going to
hace los directos jugando al forn ayer
see he has a program like a
vas a ver lleva un programa como
broncano
broncano
the hard he
lo duro
allows half the doubt I would like to see it
permite media lo duda me gustaría verlo
in situations it
en situaciones
depends a lot on my machine I love
depende mucho para mi máquina me encanta
how to do the interview it breaks my
cómo hacer la entrevista me parta la
[ __ ] I don't care who's in charge the
[__] se me da igual a quien lleve el
other one took him to a trench he's more
otro le llevó a una trinchera es más
Suarez who for me will always be Elena from
suárez que para mí siempre será elena de
dear teacher and it's that it breaks my
querido maestro y es que me parte la
[ __ ] look at that woman was boring well the
suya mira que la mujer aburría pues el
game after that work will be about being a
partido después ya trabajo será de ser
broncano and it depends on what the
broncano y depende de lo que fuera el
program was to trust you
programa para fiar cabo
can put Aurum plate presenting the
puede poner aurum plate presentando el
program but if the subject matter the
programa pero si la temática el
content is not going to interest the
contenido no va a interesar a la
audience there won't be any
audiencia no lo va a haber
understand then what does an
entiende entonces que hace un programa
interview program like as a local be a broncano
de entrevista como local sé broncano
so that they want this from here okay I'm
para que quiera esto desde aquí vale lo
going to do it  I propose and it's to piss
voy a proponer yo y es para mear
all my followers are going to send
todos mis seguidores vais a mandarle
this clip
este clip
to Telecinco and Mediaset because they are the
a telecinco y a mediaset que esos son
ones who know
los que saben
okay
vale
when you want a program that breaks
cuando queráis un programa que [__] la
television
tele
and that takes all the millions of
y que se lleve todos los millones de
viewers from YouTube to television
audiencia de youtube a la tele
and that also puts it on the internet and
y que además lo pone en internet y lo va
people from all over the world are going to watch it,
a ver gente de todo el mundo
become a Big Brother of controversial people
a ser un gran hermano de gente polémica
from YouTube
de youtube
okay controversial people Dallas good Michu
vale gente polémica el dallas buen michu
Javi Oliveira the
javi oliveira
controversial ones the toilets that
los polémicos los aseos que se encuentre
one meets the other
uno con el otro
who was going and meets Dallas there you
que iba y se encuentre con dallas ahí
have it stop with the little things Blanca from there I
tenéis dejaros de cositas blanca de ahí
'm going to be a Big Brother but of
voy a ser un gran hermano pero de
video games of video games that you give
videojuegos de videojuegos de que des
Arceo de leña Marín Peña that you put
arceo de leña marín peña que le pongáis
7 cubatas at night and in the house
7 cubata por la noche y en la casa
locked up and he drinks a cuba takes the
encerrada y se beba un cuba tarda la
bile and goes to the side and says it empathy
hiel y vaya al lado y diga se lo empatía
is what has zero empathy stop with the
es lo que tiene cero empatía dejaros de
little things this but already the allies
cositas este pero ya los aliados
positions leave him out please they
posturas dejarlo afuera por favor
are people who have that ease of
son gente que tiene esa facilidad de
speech to give it to and right now this
palabra que darle la y ahora mismo este
direct everyone who would see that
directo todo el mundo que vería ese
program you
programa
commit the reality the little that I've seen
cometes el reality lo poco que he visto
seemed a little homemade I don't know no no no
se veía un poco casero no sé no no no
the format the type of was like effort
al formato el tipo de era como esforzado
would have been it is thrown for maybe
hubiera sido está tirado para quizás
clear in the end you have both the phenomenon
claro al final tienes tanto el fenómeno
on youtube and the phenomenon that I saw more
en youtube y en fenómeno que vi más
in between and where we have all emerged they
intermedio y donde hemos surgido todos
have many elements like
nosotros tienen muchos elementos como
for example
por ejemplo
you consume this content when you want that
tu consuma este contenido cuando quieres
is to say someone who comes to watch a
es decir alguien que viene a ver un
podcast or who comes to watch your videos
podcast o que viene a ver tus vídeos lo
consumes it when who doesn't have to
consume cuando quien no se tiene que
sit in front of the TV at a certain time
sentar a la tele a una hora determinada
to watch it you know that really the
para verlo sabes que realmente la
production of the program does not depend on
producción del programa no depende de
them it is not rugby to watch partly I
ellos no es el rugby a ver en parte de
agree and partly I do not yes it is true
acuerdo y en parte no sí que es verdad
that the YouTube audience is not the
que la audiencia de youtube no son las
same people as the
mismas personas que la audiencia de la
TV audience is worth many millions of people
tele vale muchísimos millones de gente
who consume on YouTube they do not consume
que consume en youtube no consumen
television because for this very reason they are
televisión porque por esto mismo están
commenting because I arrived I
comentando porque yo llegaba yo todo me
love everything from an Aurum Play video now at
quiero de un vídeo de aurum play ahora a
11 at night I watch it and if I want to watch it it does
la 11 la noche lo veo y si lo quiero ver
in the afternoon the late on
hace de la tarde los hasta tarde en la
TV not on the Ortiz TV that I see I don't know
tele no en la tele ortiz que vea no sé
that they record it, for example I recorded it
que lo graben yo por ejemplo lo grabó
with Vodafone Place the dessert that
con el vodafone place la postre que en
live I left it for and I'll watch it when we
directo la dejó para y la veo cuando
finished the live well but I
terminamos el directo bueno pero yo te
can guarantee you
puedo garantizar
that if you put on a program that people
que si tú pones un programa que la gente
are morbid about and want to watch it, it's going to be
tiene morbo y lo quiere ver van a ser
because it's available at whatever time the
por está disponible a la hora que sea la
people who watch Temptation Island
gente que ve la isla de las tentaciones
when that's powerful Estefanía I'm
cuando eso está potente estefanía yo te
telling you that people get it at nine
digo a ti que la gente coge a las nueve
at night they're putting the kids
de la noche están metiendo a los niños
to bed Senate and with the pipe
en la cama senado y con la pipa
waiting the program starts let's
esperando empieza el programa
see here it's about one thing you do
a ver aquí se trata de una cosa
n't have to create content
no tienes que crear un contenido
and have people watch it you have to create you
y que la gente lo vea tienes que crear
don't have to do this it's like when
no tienes que hacer esto es como cuando
for example
por ejemplo
like for example when people
como por ejemplo cuando la gente hace
spam
spam
when YouTube that's put on please
cuando youtube que se pone por favor
give me a chance and visit my channel
darme una oportunidad y visitar mi canal
please
por favor
watch my video I made a video
mirad mi vídeo he hecho un vídeo por
please that's sad
favor eso es triste
you don't have to create a video and
tú no tienes que crear un vídeo y
ask people please
pedirle a la gente por favor que te
do you the favor of watching it no you're the one who
hagan el favor de verlo no tú eres el
does the favor to people of creating
que le hace el favor a la gente de crear
the content that they are looking forward to seeing do you
el contenido que están deseando de ver
understand me
me entiendes
the people are the ones who ask you please to do
la gente es la que te pide por favor que
that not you who does it and people have
hagas eso no tú que lo hace y la gente
allied themselves play
se han aliado al play
come on now  I did you a favor, not seen, no,
venga ya te hecho el favor ya no visto
no, and if you create a program that
no no y si tú creas un programa que la
people are watching and on top of that, the
gente está echando velo y encima el
program leaves you with the intrigue wanting to
programa te deja con la intriga deseando
see it the next day, I curse the
de verlo al día siguiente me cago en los
dead, it has been made to me to see if
muertos de largo se me ha hecho a ver si
tomorrow they are going to show Christopher the
mañana le van a poner a christopher las
images
imágenes
and his team editing, no, but they are
y su equipo editando no sino que es
television people with a
gente de televisión con un
conditioning in the format, you know that it has to
condicionamiento en el formato sabes que
be linked to certain things and it
tiene que estar ligado a ciertas cosas e
even loses that romantic part. Say,
incluso pierde esa parte romántica decir
[ __ ], you're in your room, I'm in
[__] tú estás en tu habitación yo estoy
my room, we're making a
mi habitación estamos haciendo un
three-hour podcast that in life is never going to
podcast de tres horas que en la vida va
be on television,
a estar en televisión
Javier Estación, or I can't see you, no
javier estación o no te puedo ver no
honey, thank you very much for your hanger, but
cariño muchas gracias por su percha pero
the problem
el problema
[Applause]
[Aplausos]
in television, never, never, never know
en televisión jamás nunca nunca se sabe
if there are production companies that you never know,
si los hay productoras que nunca se sabe
like I say, speaking, you never know, life
como digo al habla nunca se sabe la vida
takes many turns, but I hope Jordi Data,
da muchas vueltas pero ojalá jordi data
yes, his Tasir rap, since you don't see the
si ya su rap de tasir ya que no veáis
direct that it takes, that they called you
directito que lleva que te llamaron a ti
before the rough gamer birth, that there is
antes que el rudo parto gamer que hay
a production company interested in your podcast
una productora interesa en tu podcast
when I want to get the exclusive, I think there are
cuando quiero sacar la exclusiva creo
formats, I
que hay formatos
think there are formats that are over  all
creo que hay formatos que sobre todo
televisions like movistar plus a
televisiones como movistar plus una
resistance would have been I thought a
resistencia hubiera sido pensaba una
resistance an age a program
resistencia una una edad un programa
where the interviewer has no [ __ ]
donde el entrevistador no tiene ni [__]
idea who is coming and asks him hey you
idea de quién viene y le pregunta oye tú
listen to me and the weather has been good
escúchame y el tiempo que ha hecho bueno
no no it would not have been possible I think it would have been
no no no hubiera sido posible yo creo
impossible unthinkable a
que hubiera sido imposible impensable un
program the resistance jordi
programa la resistencia jordi
has ever seen buenafuente
ha visto alguna vez a buenafuente
has seen the usual te motive chronicle
ha visto la te motive habitual crónica
marciana
marciana
papito sálvame de luxe
papito sálvame de luxe
formats like this one of interview or
de formatos como éste de entrevista o
long talk can work
charla larga pueden funcionar
perfectly but I am sincere I mean
perfectamente pero yo soy sincera o sea
I am sincere and I say really when
soy sincero y digo realmente cuando
we talk about the success of the resistance or
hablamos del éxito de la resistencia o
the success of modern life we ​​are
el éxito de la vida moderna estamos
talking about the success of a
hablando del éxito de un formato de
radio format and a television format because I
radio y una de televisión porque yo lo
consume it on youtube maybe if the
consumo en youtube ya lo mejor si la
resistance were only on movistar or
resistencia sólo estuviera en movistar o
modern life only on the radio and I
la vida moderna sólo en la radio y la
think modern life is top 223 on
vida moderna creo que es top 223 en
spotify podcasts that is to say it works well at the
spotify podcast es decir funciona bien a
audio level, I mean it is
nivel de a nivel de audio o sea que es
a format that works well also at the
un formato que funciona bien también a
level but equally on the platforms
nivel pero igualmente en las plataformas
apart, I mean that no longer you go to do to
aparte o sea que no ya no acudes al
listen to it with yaya and the total there
hacer a escucharlo con yaya y el total
is  many things there are many
hay muchas cosas que hay muchas
variables in the media and
variables en el medio de comunicación y
everything that ends up affecting you and I believe
todo que te acaba afectando y yo creo
that in part it is the authenticity of the
que en parte en la autenticidad del
content that is made on YouTube and that
contenido que se hace en youtube y que
we are the creators
estamos nosotros los propios creadores
of this content of these formats that we will
de este contenido de estos formatos que
go with all that is what
ya iremos con todo eso es lo que atrae
also attracts part of the audience and there
también a parte de la audiencia y
is always a perception and I notice it
siempre hay una percepción y yo lo noto
with any content that
con cualquier contenido que la
television is I have been aware in
televisión es he estado enterado de
some way whether that limit is due to
alguna manera ya sea que ese límite por
the medium itself that is limited by the
el propio medio que se limite por el
format the production there is something that
formato la producción hay algo que hace
the blond does on television I don't mind and on
el rubio en televisión no me pene y en
YouTube yes I
youtube sí
think it depends on two things I am
yo creo que depende de dos cosas
going to say it I have said it before but I am
lo voy a decir yo lo he dicho antes pero
not going to say the blond on television is not
no voy a decir el rubio en televisión no
suitable for you because he does not know how to handle himself on
te pega porque no se sabe desenvolver en
a television set
un plató de televisión
on the internet in tweets he makes
en internet en tweets le hace gracia a
his fans laugh his followers who laugh at
su fan do a sus seguidores que le ríen
any chupina they make and
cualquier chupina que hagan y lo
defend him in anything he says
defienden en cualquier cosa que diga
okay but the blond Antena 3 has a
vale pero el rubio antena 3 tiene una
contestant that what has to do
concursante que lo que tiene que hacer
a guy who is supposed to be the one who already has
un tío que se supone que el que tiene ya
more more experience in the matter is
más más más tablas en el asunto es
break the ice and make the person
romper el hielo y hacer que la persona
novice feels comfortable okay when I
novata se sienta cómoda vale yo cuando
bring someone here I'm always
traigo aquí a alguien siempre estoy
breaking the ice so they feel
rompiendo el hielo para que se sienta
at home okay I bring you a
como en su casa vale te traiga una
contestant and the blonde played a
concursante y el rubio le gastó una
joke on her like that or well but you've fought
broma así o bien pero te has luchado
Osasuna that we have to be
osasuna de que tenemos que ser
aware that not all
conscientes de que no todos los
YouTubers are good for live shows too
youtubers sirven para el directo también
that's a reality too me I'm not
eso es una realidad también yo yo no
good at many things not all YouTubers are
sirvo para muchas cosas no todo youtuber
good for eye for live shows for
sirven para para ojo para directo para
a
un directo
high quality entertainment live show and
de alta calidad de entretenimiento y
high quality improvisation or high
alta calidad de improvisación o alta
quality communication I mean in
calidad de comunicación es decir en
tweets you have all kinds of live shows
tweets tienes directos de todo tipo
many of the live tweets are
muchos de los directos de tweets son
people who are there for an hour and have
gente que está durante una hora y
spoken 14 times bland and people watch it
hablado 14 veces sosa y la gente lo ve
because I already explained it for me twitch is
porque ya lo explique para mí twitch es
a way of you're not alone having it
una forma de no estás solo de tenerlo
there you have it there it accompanies you but you
ahí lo tienes ahí te va acompañando pero
're not waiting to see what
no estás pendiente de a ver qué va a
the majority of people are going to say but when you
decir la mayoría de gente pero cuando tú
watch TV what you want is a
ves la tele tú lo que quieres es un
quality product and a supposedly
producto de calidad y un des de supuesta
quality product and a product where the people who are
calidad y un producto donde la gente que
there who are involved in it have a
está ahí que está metida ahí tenga un
gift to reach you  Of course not all
don para llegar te claro no todos los
YouTubers are going to be good at this, to go
youtubers van a servir para esto para ir
to a television program and
a un programa de televisión y
present it or to be collaborators and that's why I think that
presentarlo o para ser colaboradores y
the
por eso creo que también el formato
YouTuber format on television for being a YouTuber is
youtuber en televisión por ser youtuber
not going to work it has to be a
no va a funcionar tiene que ser una
person who even if they hadn't been a
persona que aunque no hubiera sido
YouTuber and had dedicated themselves to making
youtuber y se hubiera dedicado a hacer
shoes you could have put them on
zapatos lo hubieras podido meter en la
television and it would have worked these
televisión y hubiera funcionado estos
are the ones that are going to work in that medium
son los que van a funcionar en ese medio
because I think top that immense came
porque creo que top que inmensa came
academy would have been better if
academy hubiera hubiera sido mejor si
they were at home or even
ellos estuvieran en su casa o incluso
all at one of their homes
todos en casa de uno de ellos en plan
talking like there and it would have worked
charla en plan ahí y hubiera funcionado
better than putting them in a studio
mejor que meterlos en un en un estudio
where I think you take away what you
donde creo que les quitas lo que tú
said spontaneity is that now is
decías la espontaneidad es que ahora es
the grace it corsets us if they feel a
la gracia nos encorseta si se notan un
little uncomfortable there is a there is a presenter
poco incómodos hay un hay un presentador
also the format I don't know the little that I have
también el formato no sé lo poco que he
seen it seemed tacky to me and it's a shame
visto me pareció cutre y es una pena
because the people are good there are good people
porque la gente es buena hay gente buena
involved in there where it crosses is a guy who is
metida ahí donde cruza es un tío que
also like that he is very funny and everything
también es así tiene mucha gracia y todo
but what is the format seemed to me
pero lo que es el formato me pareció de
third division to a great a Big
tercera división a un gran un gran
Brother that has nothing to do with it
hermano que no tiene que ver con el
sensationalism but a big brother
sensacionalismo pero un gran hermano de
television 'he says it's macho man I know it
televisión 'la dice es macho tío ya sé
's a nexus or a big brother of
que es un nexo o un gran hermano de
cosiv as if it were a big brother on
cosiv como si a un gran hermano en el
channel 47 those of Seville you will know you
canal 47 los de sevilla sabréis os
will remember to go every 47
acordaréis de ir cada 47
I think that the neus would say that it is not the
creo que la neus diríase que no es la
big chain but I don't know it did
gran cadena pero no sé
n't give me very good it aspires to maybe it
no me dio muy buena aspira a lo mejor
comes back and then wins they win in speed
remonta y luego gana ganan en velocidad
and it is the support in vinegar but from the start I'm
y es la apoya en vinagre pero de entrada
not glad I didn't go
no me alegro de no haber seguido
ahead with the talks the truth is I'm
adelante con las charlas la verdad me
glad I wouldn't have liked it even if I
alegro no hubiera gustado aunque lo
had done it I would have gone home I would have
hubiera hecho me hubiera ido a casa lo
seen it and I would have said
hubiera visto y hubiera dicho
no of course I wouldn't be proud
no claro no estaría orgulloso
but well we'll see what happens with let's see
pero bueno veremos lo que pasa con a ver
how I continue with this I hope and I hope it
como continuo con esto ojalá y ojalá que
goes very well because there are people
vaya muy bien porque hay gente que hay
inside who are acquaintances of mine and I
dentro que son conocidos míos y que
hope that they do well because they are very
espero que les vaya bien porque son muy
good people the recognition is a
buena gente el reconocimiento es un
recognition of the people on the internet
reconocimiento a la gente de internet
who have grown on the internet and who move a
que ha crecido en internet y que mueve a
lot of people I mean having a
mucha gente es decir que tener un
television space is simple they
espacio de televisión es sencillo
trust you for a project like
que confíen en ti para un proyecto como
that is cool but depending yes but  as you
eso mola pero en función sí pero como
well know what it's worth I don't know who
bien sabes de lo que vale no sé quién es
this man is his
este hombre
name is not but well the case through
no se llama pero bueno el caso a través
what it's worth to give a space on
de lo que vale que le dé un espacio en
television to these people and with the blond and
televisión a esta gente y con el rubio y
say you shower and then the other one from
diga tú te duchas y luego el otro por
behind says hey ere a designer what is it that
detrás diga oye ere diseñadora que es
you can design something for this sexy body
que podrás diseñar algo para este cuerpo
well it's in demand I had in the end
pues está demandado yo tuve al final
as always like when win michu takes
como siempre como cuando coge win michu
and makes a film or when the
y hace una película o cuando coge el
other one takes the ratio was or when you take Memphis they
otro iba la ratio o cuando coges memphis
always don't give it to you
siempre no te lo dan
after talking tertiary
tras hablar terciarias
on antenna 3 that they give them a plate
en antena 3 que les den un plato de un
of a million euros to a pasta production with caro but they give them a bit of a thing with trilla what happened with the chiringuito that came out of a 'point pelota' of I don't know what that you didn't even see the tato at first and by art with
el tato en un principio y por arte con
a plate of [ __ ] they managed to get to
un plato de [__] consiguieron llegar
where they are now the chiringuito of
donde lo que son ahora el chiringuito de
gamers that has an audience that
jugones que tiene una audiencia que
flips out this doesn't usually happen regularly
flipas esto no suele pasar habitualmente
and there were very good people in
y ahí había gente muy buena de
journalism I had satins I to Pedrerol
periodismo tenía satenes yo a pedrerol
who is a  a crack of journalism and a
que es un crack del periodismo y un
crack of the ease of cleanliness that
crack del de la facilidad de desaseo eso
is not normal normal is that these
no es lo normal normal es que es estos
programs that are on this type of
programas que están en este tipo de
television are anecdotal which is a
televisiones sean anecdóticos que es una
shame but being anecdotal the chiringuito
pena pero ser anecdóticos el chiringuito
like that a bit is a separate case well
así un poco es un caso aparte bueno
we will see what happens with each thousand I wish you
veremos qué pasa con cada mil os deseo
the best I really hope it works
lo mejor de verdad espero que funcione
well but I also have to be realistic
bien pero también tengo que ser realista
I give my opinion and what a product looks at you have to
doy mi opinión y lo que un producto mira
know you have to know each one
hay que saber hay que saber cada uno
where you have a limit okay as
dónde tienes un límite vale como bien ha
Jordi has said one thing I have grasped of the little I have
dicho jordi una cosa captado de lo poco
grasped
captado
I agree with him there has been that the
de acuerdo yo con él ahí ha sido que la
person who is worth to be on a
persona que vale para estar un plató de
television set bullfighting there to whatever comes
televisión toreando ahí a lo que venga
all kinds of situations in a live
todo tipo de situaciones en un directo
bullfighting that something unexpected comes to you
toreando que te viene un improvisto que
a guest goes crazy and puts his
un invitado se vuelve loco y mete la
foot in it and you have to cover up put a patch
pata y tienes que tapar poner un parche
here I came out there make it funny
aquí salí por allá que la hagas gracia
break the ice here break the
que rompa el hielo por aquí que rompa el
thread there the person who is worth for
hilo por allá la persona que vale para
that would be worth it even if it had been YouTube
eso valdría aunque hubiera sido youtube
or even if it had been a shoemaker because he
o aunque hubiera sido zapatero porque lo
has it okay he already has it  it's okay
tiene vale lo tiene ya está vale sin
however all youtubers are useless
embargo todos los youtubers no sirve
look when someone comes from television to
mira cuando viene alguien de la tele a
youtube many people are not good for
youtube mucha gente no valen para
youtube the journalists the
youtube los periodistas los
presenters normally do
presentadores normalmente hacen
any nonsense on youtube and they succeed
cualquier tontería en youtube y triunfan
and it is eaten up on youtube because because they are
y se come en youtube porque porque están
used to television and now you come to
acostumbrada a la tele y ahora vienes a
youtube
youtube
what is the edited video you edit it how you want
qué es el vídeo editado lo edita cómo te
manage your content what is
da la gana maneja tu contenido lo que es
sport they eat it look at angel martin
sport se lo comen mira del ángel martín
who is a presenter of I know what
que es un presentador de sé lo que
you did the only summer that
hiciste el único verano que a mí ese
man I never liked much anymore
hombre no me nunca más simpatizado mucho
however now I don't know if it's because he
sin embargo ahora no sé si es que no
is not working with what he is doing
está trabajando con lo que está haciendo
but in the morning he does like a small
pero por la mañana hace como un pequeño
morning show on twitter a two
matinal en twitter un vídeo de dos
minute video on twitter giving the news
minutos en twitter dando las noticias
the folders not on twitter doing that
las carpetas no en twitter haciendo esa
nonsense the chapitas no because because
tontería los chapitas no porque porque
a guy who is on a television set
un tío que está en un plató de
at noon handling a lot of salt
al mediodía manejando un montón de sal
I know or I don't know the program white gigi come on
se o no programa blanquito de gigi venga
play the oven there here you have fought and
juega el forn hay aquí te has luchado y
that fed up come well the crazy head you have to
que harta venga bien el cabeza loca hay
put the red color above the
que poner el color rojo encima del
yellow don't salt or put you in
amarillo no sal se o que te ponga en
uncomfortable situations okay  that on the
situaciones incómodas vale que a la
street a topic is uncomfortable to
calle una temas está incómodo a la
jail donated I went out with it's not going to be
cárcel donaba salí con no va a ser
Gonzalez but the house between this you have
gonzález pero la casa entre esto tienes
a bald ass and knows how to get out of all kinds
el culo pelado y sabe salir de todo tipo
of situations good a Jorge Javier
de situaciones buena un jorge javier
doing a live on YouTube and he eats
haciendo un directo en youtube y se come
twitch because it's that he eats the set
twitch porque sea que se come el plató
of Sálvame
de sálvame
now your poor audio you see on TV
ahora tu pobre audio tu ver en la tele
for the simple fact that he has numbers
por el simple hecho de que tiene números
of followers and you always eat a
de seguidores y os coméis siempre una
[ __ ] [ __ ] the eyebrow
[__] [__] el ceja
I just remembered the sea because there I
me acabo de acordar del sea porque allí
saw the movie of Santiago Segura which is
vi la película de santiago segura que es
very good the movie of Santiago Segura
buenísima la película de santiago segura
the 1st the 2nd very good the eyebrow that thanks
la 1 la 2 buenísima el ceja que gracias
to a guy who plays a chav and a
a un tío que hace de cani y de niñato de
neighborhood brat says the one in peto that this method
barrio dice el de peto a que este método
shuffles a million followers in
baraja a un millón de seguidores en
urging videos on YouTube it's not worth it what it's
instar a vídeos en youtube no lo vale
going to be on YouTube what is he going to
que va a ser sea en youtube que nos va a
tell us the sea
contar el sea
in esteem nobody sees it it
en estima no lo ve nadie
was a wedding of a grace like the
fue una boda de una gracia como el
typical meme when the meme of a video comes out that they will
típico meme cuando sale el meme de un
exhibit him like the black guy
vídeo que se exhibirán el como el negro
with the dick or how  will continue this
de la [__] o cómo va a seguir este
same video at 720 the track but then you are
mismo vídeo a 720 la pista pero luego tú
not going to sit down when you get off
no te vas a sentar cuando tú salgas del
work and you were with your wife you are
trabajo y te pongas era con tu mujer tú
not going to sit down and watch a couple of
no te vas a sentar a verte un par de
hours at the eyebrow you are going to see someone who
horas al ceja tú vas a ver a alguien que
is telling you things that entertain you
te esté contando cosas que te entretenga
that I don't know what to have as soon as you are not
que no sé qué que tener en cuanto tú no
going to see eyebrow and eyebrow they put it on Big
va a ver ceja y ceja lo meten en gran
Brother [ __ ] [ __ ] [ __ ]
hermano [__] [__]
[ __ ] zero charisma personality did not
[__] [__] cero carisma personalidad no
impose no no he did not have content or
se imponía no no no tenía contenido ni
six in Big Brother I without Big Brother
seis en gran hermano yo sin gran hermano
sang about you
se cantó de ti
and like that I can mention like that about
y como eso te puedo mencionar así así de
U2 see that they have taken them to television and
u2 ver que los han llevado a la tele y
on television no they are worthless okay and
en la tele no no valen para nada vale y
on YouTube and on Instagram influencers
a youtube y en instagram influencers
YouTube is small and Instagram is
a youtube es pequeños e instagram es
influencers who have gone to programs have
influencers que han ido a programas han
gone to comment on the Big Brother debate
ido a comentar el debate de gran hermano
that I have seen I have gone to Sálvame they have
que lo he visto yo han ido a sálvame han
gone to things and they have jumped [ __ ] great
ido a cosas y han saltado de [__] madre
the problem is that there has not been a
el problema es que no ha habido una
person
persona
a producer with someone who has the
una productora con alguien que tenga la
idea that has yet to be known how to
idea que todavía ya se haya sabido qué
square it because I think that  to
cuadrarlo porque yo creo que para
square that you have to know the world
cuadrar eso tienes que conocer el mundo
I had the world of television to fall
yo tuviera el mundo de la tele para caer
for these things
en estas cosas
because I as a viewer
porque yo como espectador
already look at the moment you tell me what
ya mira en el momento que me dices de lo
the whole gaimer academy is about between
que trata el todo gaimer academy entre
the youtubers that go and on the chain of
los youtubers que van y en la cadena de
la mancha I have told him [ __ ] [ __ ]
la mancha yo le ha dicho [__] [__]
[ __ ] garbage without seeing it [ __ ] garbage
[__] basura sin verlo putísima basura
and injuring from here the key managed
y lesionando de aquí la clave gestionada
from here the key that would be the triumph
de aquí la clave que sería el triunfo
on telecinco
en telecinco
in prime time
en prime time
a [ __ ] big brother of the youtubers of
un [__] gran hermano de los youtubers de
controversies okay
polémicas vale
Andre geim plate enter the big
andre geim plate entre a la casa de gran
brother house sits on the couch waiting for
hermano se sienta en el sofá esperando a
whoever mantra and suddenly through the
quien mantra y de repente por la ventana
back window wind and bird
de atrás entra wind y bird
la wind enter and the truth is I end up in the
la wind y la verdad me acabo en la punta
dry point or the kick that I'm leaving we
seca o la patada que me voy
continue with live and life
seguimos con live and life
and I already say me
y ya digo yo
and I sink the unam and I will do the fat al sion
y yo hunda la unam y haré yo los al sión
the fat moose
los alces gordos
and I tell you
y yo os digo
that everyone accepts
que todos aceptan
everyone would accept if they are on youtube
todos aceptarían si están en youtube
how are they not going to accept
como no van a aceptar
with 15 15 20 and 30 thousand euros of pan
con 15 15 20 y 30 mil euros de pan
american
american
prove it give this video everything  the
demostrarlo darle a este vídeo todo el
world that I would see in that program
mundo que vería en ese programa
if you have reached this point of course well
si habéis llega hasta aquí por supuesto
guys
bueno chicos